joshmorony.com 2019-08-07

# Privacy Policy | joshmorony - Learn Ionic & Build Mobile Apps with Web Tech

This document outlines the privacy policy for this website. We will always treat any information you supply on this website with respect. Any information requested or used will be done so with the goal of improving your experience on this website.

**Does this website use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We work with third parties to serve advertisements and content targeted to users’ interests.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Information Regarding GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)

As of May 25, 2018 this website will comply with the [EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://www.eugdpr.org/). These regulations were implemented by the European Union, and apply to users of this website who reside within the European Union. These regulations provide a set of protections for the data that websites collect about you. Although these regulations only apply specifically to users from within the European Union, this website will extend similar protections to all users on this website.

Under these regulations, your rights include:

  * The right to understand what information is being collected
  * How that information is being used, and why
  * The option to opt out of any data collection, and have your personal data deleted
  * The option to receive from this website any personally identifiable information that you have supplied

The only time when personally identifiable information about you will be collected on this website is when you willingly supply it willingly. Simply accessing and viewing the pages of this website will not require you to supply any personal information, nor will you be knowingly tracked in such a way that you could be personally identified.

**What information is being collected?**

Throughout your use of this website, types of personally identifiable information you may optionally be asked to provide are:

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Your website address
  * Your preferences and responses to survey questions
  * Payment information (if you are purchasing products, this data will not be stored on this website)

Additional personally identifiable information may also be stored based on your interactions with the website if you have opted in to the mailing list or have bought products including:

  * Specific products that you have purchased
  * Specific pages on the website that you have visisted

**Where is the information stored?**

All personal information that is collected through this website will be stored with one of our service providers. You can find details about each of these providers later in this document.

**How will the information be used?**

Primarily, the personal information that you supply will be used for communication, targetting content, and to facilitate the sale (and refunds) of any products that you might purchase through this website. A detailed list of how types of data will be used is available later in this document.

**Who will the information be shared with?**

Any personal data collected through this website will never be sold to any 3rd party. The only 3rd party companies that will have access to any personal data related to this website will be the data processors that are outlined below. These data processors are used solely to help facilitate the function and operation of this website.

**How long will the information be stored?**

Data will be stored for an indeterminate amount of time, but it may be deleted at any time without notice. You may also request to have your data deleted at any time.

### 3rd Party Tools This Website Uses

**Google Analytics**

This website has enabled the IP Anonymization feature of Google Analytics. This prevents personally identifiable information from being stored on the Google Analytics servers in relation to your interactions with this website. If you would like to know more about IP Anonymization you can [click here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en)

**ConvertKit**

This website uses ConvertKit in order to facilitate collecting email addresses and sending emails. Providing your email address is entirely optional, but if you choose to do so, it may be used to send you the following types of emails:

  * Newsletter/update emails
  * Occasional promotional emails
  * Course/sequence educational emails

This website is committed to sending content of value, and you will never be sent spam or any promotions that are not relevant. Promotional emails will be sent very infrequently, and will only ever be of products or services that we believe will be of genuine interest to you. You can be completely removed from the mailing list at any time.

Depending on your interactions with emails that you receive, or actions you take on the website, your records in ConvertKit may be “tagged” with additional information. This information may be used to indicate:

  * The types of content you wish to receive notifications about via email
  * The volume of emails you would prefer to receive
  * Your responses to any surveys/polls that may be conducted (generally this is used to help determine the kind of content that is added to the website)
  * Any products you have purchased
  * Specific pages on the website that you have visited
  * Specific forms or sequences that you signed up to on the website

**SendOwl**

If you purchase one of the products available on this website, the purchase will be facilitated by SendOwl. Depending on the option you choose for payment, the transaction will be processed by either PayPal or Stripe. This website does not store any information related to payment processing, but these external services may.

When you purchase a product, your email will be stored in order to send you updates for the product, but you will not be added to the general mailing list unless you specifically choose to be added to it. You may opt out of product updates at any time.

**Disqus**

The comments on this website are made available through the [Disqus](https://disqus.com/) comments system. Any personal information that you decide to supply through the comments system will be stored on their servers.

**RightMessage**

This tool is used to provide personalised content based on your specific interests (determined by your responses to optional survey questions or by other pages you have visited on the website). If you have opted in to the mailing list for this website, then the data associated with this tool will be personally identifiable (you can, however, unsubscribe from the mailing list at any time if you wish).

No personally identifiable information is stored on RightMessage’s servers.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 11/07/2019

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

privacy@joshmorony.com

Mobirony

P.O. Box 221, Seacliff Park

Adelaide, South Australia 5049

Australia

Parts of this privacy policy were generated using Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support [help desk software](http://www.rhinosupport.com/).
